Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 2: Legislative Committee Files. 1954-1994
    - Subseries 15: Judiciary, 1976-1994
      - Judiciary: Courts, 1971-1994
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Select Committee on Narcotics. 1977-1980 (Box 245, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Select Committee on Narcotics. 1978-1980 (Box 245, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Select Committee on Narcotics. 1978-1987 (Box 245, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Select Committee on Narcotics. 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 14-16)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Select Committee on Narcotics. 1980 (Box 245, Folder 17-18)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Southeast Asia and Bo Gritz. 1985-1989 (Box 245, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Southwest Border States Information Sharing. 1992 (Box 245, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, State and Local Assistance. 1984-1988 (Box 245, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Drug Enforcement, Syria. 1991-1992 (Box 245, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Drunk Driving. 1979-1990 (Box 245, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Embassy Protests. 1985-1986 (Box 246, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Embassy Protests. 1985-1988 (Box 246, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Employee Retirement Income Security Act. 1985 (Box 246, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Environmental Venue. 1979-1982 (Box 246, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1977-1980 (Box 246, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1978-1984 (Box 246, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1979-1984 (Box 246, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1979-1994 (Box 246, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1981 (Box 246, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1983 (Box 246, Folder 10-13)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1983-1984 (Box 246, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1984-1986 (Box 246, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Equal Access to Justice. 1988 (Box 246, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1979-1982 (Box 246, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1979-1982 (Box 246, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1981-1987 (Box 246, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1983 (Box 246, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1984 (Box 246, Folder 21-22)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1984-1987 (Box 246, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Exclusionary Rule. 1987 (Box 247, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Extradition. 1981-1983 (Box 247, Folder 2)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1979 (Box 247, Folder 3)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1979-1980 (Box 247, Folder 4)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1985-1986 (Box 247, Folder 5-7)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1986 (Box 247, Folder 8)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1989 (Box 247, Folder 9)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1992 (Box 247, Folder 10)
        - Courts, False Claims Act. 1992-1994 (Box 247, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Federal Bureau of Investigation. 1978-1986 (Box 247, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Federal Bureau of Investigation. 1987 (Box 247, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Federal Bureau of Investigation. 1988 (Box 247, Folder 14-15)
        - Courts, Federal Bureau of Investigation. 1991-1993 (Box 247, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Federal Bureau of Investigation Oversight. 1990-1994 (Box 247, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Federal Courts. 1977 (Box 247, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Federal Courts. 1987 (Box 247, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals. 1977-1979 (Box 247, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals. 1983-1984 (Box 247, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals. 1989-1990 (Box 247, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals. 1989-1991 (Box 247, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1978-1981 (Box 247, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1978-1984 (Box 247, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1978-1987 (Box 248, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1978-1988 (Box 248, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1978-1989 (Box 248, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1983 (Box 248, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1983-1985 (Box 248, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1983-1987 (Box 248, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1985-1986 (Box 248, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1987 (Box 248, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1987-1990 (Box 248, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1991-1992 (Box 248, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Supreme Court. 1993 (Box 248, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, Study Commission. 1982-1988 (Box 248, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, U.S. Claims Court. 1987 (Box 248, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Federal Courts, U.S. Court of Military Appeals. 1979 (Box 248, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Federal Courts Improvement Act. 1979 (Box 248, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Federal Courts Improvement Act. 1979-1981 (Box 248, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Federal Courts Improvement Act, DeConcini Law Review Article. 1991 (Box 248, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Federal Employees Liability Reform. 1988 (Box 248, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships. 1977 (Box 248, Folder 19-20)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships. 1977-1979 (Box 248, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships. 1978-1980 (Box 248, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships. 1986-1994 (Box 248, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships. 1987-1991 (Box 248, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships, Claiborne Impeachment. 1986 (Box 248, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships, Claiborne Impeachment. 1986-1988 (Box 248, Folder 26)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships, Court of International Trade. 1990 (Box 248, Folder 27)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships, Hastings Impeachment. 1989 (Box 248, Folder 28)
        - Courts, Federal Judgeships, Nixon Impeachment. 1988-1989 (Box 248, Folder 29)
        - Courts, Federal Magistrates. 1986 (Box 249, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Federal Neutrality Act. 1983 (Box 249, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Federal Regulatory Reform. 1984 (Box 249, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Federal Tort Claims Act. 1983 (Box 249, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Federal Tort Claims Act. 1990-1992 (Box 249, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Federal Tort Claims Act, Feres Doctrine. 1984-1988 (Box 249, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Federal Tort Liability Repeal. 1986-1989 (Box 249, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Female Offenders. no date (Box 249, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Foreign Corrupt Practices Act. 1981 (Box 249, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Forfeiture Act. 1983 (Box 249, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Forfeiture Act. 1985-1986 (Box 249, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Freedom of Information Act Amendments. 1979-1987 (Box 249, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Gaming Advertising. 1983-1988 (Box 249, Folder 13)
        - Courts, General. 1977-1978 (Box 249, Folder 14-15)
        - Courts, General. 1977-1980 (Box 249, Folder 16-17)
        - Courts, General. 1978-1979 (Box 249, Folder 18)
        - Courts, General. 1978-1980 (Box 249, Folder 19-20)
        - Courts, General. 1978-1985 (Box 249, Folder 21)
        - Courts, General. 1979-1980 (Box 249, Folder 22)
        - Courts, General. 1979-1992 (Box 249, Folder 23)
        - Courts, General. 1980-1982 (Box 249, Folder 24)
        - Courts, General. 1982 (Box 249, Folder 25)
        - Courts, General. 1984-1989 (Box 249, Folder 26)
        - Courts, Genocide Convention. 1987-1988 (Box 249, Folder 27)
        - Courts, Grand Jury Secrecy. 1983-1984 (Box 249, Folder 28)
        - Courts, Grand Jury Secrecy. 1985-1988 (Box 249, Folder 29)
        - Courts, Grandparent Visitation Rights. 1983 (Box 250, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Habeas Corpus Reform. 1977-1980 (Box 250, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Habeas Corpus Reform. 1983-1986 (Box 250, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Habeas Corpus Reform. 1985-1986 (Box 250, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Hanigan Case. 1977-1980 (Box 250, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Hanigan Case. 1981 (Box 250, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Hobbs Act Amendment, Union Violence. 1982-1986 (Box 250, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Identities Protection Act. 1980 (Box 250, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Independent Counsel. 1987-1988 (Box 250, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Independent Counsel. 1987-1993 (Box 250, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Indian Jurisdiction. 1977 (Box 250, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Indigent Defense. 1984 (Box 250, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Indigent Defense. 1985-1986 (Box 250, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Iran-Contra Affair. 1986-1987 (Box 250, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Iran-Contra Affair. 1987 (Box 250, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Iran-Contra Affair. 1988 (Box 250, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Iran-Contra Affair. 1989 (Box 250, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Insanity Defense. 1982 (Box 250, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Insanity Defense. 1982-1984 (Box 251, Folder 1)
        - Courts, INSLAW Case. 1992-1993 (Box 251, Folder 2)
        - Courts, INSLAW Case. 1993 (Box 251, Folder 3-4)
        - Courts, Judges. 1989-1990 (Box 251, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Judicial Bias. 1994 (Box 251, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Judicial Branch Improvements Act. 1984-1986 (Box 251, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Judicial Branch Improvements Act. 1987-1988 (Box 251, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Judicial Branch Improvements Act. 1988 (Box 251, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Judicial Branch Improvements Act. 1990 (Box 251, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Judicial Conference Sunshine Act. 1978-1980 (Box 251, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Judicial Conference Sunshine Act. 1979-1980 (Box 251, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Judicial Conference Sunshine Act. 1980-1981 (Box 251, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Judicial Conduct and Disability Act. 1979-1980 (Box 251, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Judicial Discipline. 1980-1992 (Box 251, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Judicial Discipline. 1986 (Box 251, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Judicial Immunity. 1988-1989 (Box 251, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Judicial Pay Raise. 1989 (Box 251, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Judicial Taxation. 1990-1993 (Box 251, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Judicial Tenure. 1977-1978 (Box 251, Folder 20-21)
        - Courts, Judicial Tenure. 1979 (Box 251, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Jury Fees. no date (Box 251, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Justice Assistance Act. 1981-1984 (Box 252, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Justice Assistance Act. 1982-1983 (Box 252, Folder 2)
        - Courts, John F. Kennedy Assassination Materials Disclosure Act. 1992 (Box 252, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Rodney King verdict. 1992 (Box 252, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement. 1979-1980 (Box 252, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement. 1991-1994 (Box 252, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement. 1992-1993 (Box 252, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement, Body Armor. 1990 (Box 252, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement, Claims. 1989 (Box 252, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement, Railroad and University Police. 1985-1986 (Box 252, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration. 1978-1980 (Box 252, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Law Related Education. 1989 (Box 252, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Legal Services Corporation. 1985-1988 (Box 252, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Legal Services Corporation. 1989-1990 (Box 252, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Lobbying Reform. 1986 (Box 252, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Lobbying Reform. 1986-1988 (Box 252, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Magistrates. 1977 (Box 252, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Magistrates. 1979-1980 (Box 252, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Magistrates. 1986 (Box 252, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Major Fraud Act. 1985-1987 (Box 252, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Major Fraud Act. 1987-1988 (Box 252, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Major Fraud Act. 1988 (Box 252, Folder 22-24)
        - Courts, Major Fraud Act. 1989 (Box 252, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Mail Order Martial Arts Weapons. 1985-1986 (Box 252, Folder 26)
        - Courts, Media Coverage of Rape Trials. 1984 (Box 252, Folder 27)
        - Courts, Medical Malpractice. 1986-1989 (Box 252, Folder 28)
        - Courts, Military Medical Malpractice. 1988 (Box 252, Folder 29)
        - Courts, Minor and Technical Criminal Law Amendments. 1988 (Box 253, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Missing Children Act. 1982-1984 (Box 253, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Motor Voter Bill. 1993 (Box 253, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Mulit-Party Forum Shopping for Appellate Review. 1985-1987 (Box 253, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Municipal Liability. 1981-1983 (Box 253, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Oliver North Prosecution. 1989 (Box 253, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Office of Special Investigations. 1980-1982 (Box 253, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Office of Special Investigations. 1983-1984 (Box 253, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Office of Special Investigations. 1984 (Box 253, Folder 9-10)
        - Courts, Office of Special Investigations. 1985 (Box 253, Folder 11-12)
        - Courts, Office of Special Investigations. 1986-1987 (Box 253, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Ombudsman. 1977 (Box 253, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Ombudsman. 1977-1980 (Box 253, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Ombudsman. 1981-1987 (Box 253, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Ombudsman. 1989-1991 (Box 253, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Ombudsman. 1990-1991 (Box 253, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1977-1979 (Box 253, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1977-1980 (Box 254, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1978-1981 (Box 254, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1978-1982 (Box 254, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1979 (Box 254, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1979-1980 (Box 254, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1981 (Box 254, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1981-1982 (Box 254, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1983 (Box 254, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1984 (Box 254, Folder 9-10)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1984-1989 (Box 254, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1988 (Box 254, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Organized Crime. 1988-1989 (Box 254, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Pardons-Shibley, George. 1977-1979 (Box 254, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Pardons-Stoll, Charles Steward. 1975-1978 (Box 254, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Parimutuel Licensing. 1987-1989 (Box 254, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Personnel. 1980 (Box 254, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Pollard Spy Case. 1988-1993 (Box 254, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1977-1985 (Box 254, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1977-1991 (Box 254, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1980-1982 (Box 254, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1982-1986 (Box 254, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1985-1986 (Box 254, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1987-1990 (Box 255, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Pornography. 1987-1992 (Box 255, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Pre-Trial Services Act. 1980-1981 (Box 255, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1977-1981 (Box 255, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1977-1989 (Box 255, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1978-1987 (Box 255, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1987-1988 (Box 255, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1992-1993 (Box 255, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Prisons. 1993-1994 (Box 255, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Prisons, Arizona. 1988-1989 (Box 255, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Private Relief Bills. 1979-1991 (Box 255, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Private Relief Bills. 1983 (Box 255, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Private Relief Bills. 1985-1986 (Box 255, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Private Relief Bills. 1988-1992 (Box 255, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Product Liability. 1986 (Box 255, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Product Liability. 1989-1990 (Box 255, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Product Liability. 1992-1994 (Box 255, Folder 18-19)
        - Courts, Project Alert. 1989-1993 (Box 255, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Public Corruption. 1987-1989 (Box 255, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Quiet Title Act. 1986 (Box 255, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Racial Justice Act. 1994 (Box 255, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1984-1985 (Box 255, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1984-1986 (Box 255, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1984-1990 (Box 255, Folder 26)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1985-1986 (Box 255, Folder 27-28)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1986 (Box 256, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1986-1987 (Box 256, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1986-1988 (Box 256, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1987 (Box 256, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1987-1988 (Box 256, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1987-1989 (Box 256, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1988-1989 (Box 256, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1989 (Box 256, Folder 8-10)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1989-1990 (Box 256, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1989-1991 (Box 256, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO). 1993 (Box 256, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Radiation Exposure Compensation Act. 1986-1989 (Box 256, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Rao Federal Building, U.S. Court of International Trade. 1984 (Box 256, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Recovery of Health Costs. 1985 (Box 256, Folder 16)
        - Courts, Regulatory Reform. 1978-1983 (Box 256, Folder 17)
        - Courts, Regulatory Reform. 1980-1984 (Box 256, Folder 18)
        - Courts, Rules Changes. 1986-1994 (Box 256, Folder 19)
        - Courts, Rulemaking Process. no date (Box 256, Folder 20)
        - Courts, Secret Service Reform Act. 1981 (Box 256, Folder 21)
        - Courts, Serious Non-violent Offenses. 1983 (Box 256, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Son of Sam Statute. 1992-1993 (Box 256, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Subcommittee Office Plan. 1983 (Box 256, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Sports Lottery Ban. 1990-1992 (Box 256, Folder 25)
        - Courts, State Justice Institute. 1987 (Box 256, Folder 26)
        - Courts, Subcommittee on Improvements in Judicial Machinery. 1980 (Box 256, Folder 27-28)
        - Courts, Superfund Improvement Act. 1985 (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
        - Courts, Superior Court Judgeships. 1979 (Box 257, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Telemarketing Fraud. 1989-1993 (Box 257, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Telephone Monitoring by Employers. 1987-1988 (Box 257, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Telephone Taping. 1984 (Box 257, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Television Programming of Offensive Material. 1989 (Box 257, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Terrorism. 1982-1991 (Box 257, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Terrorism. 1984-1985 (Box 257, Folder 9-10)
        - Courts, Terrorism. 1985 (Box 257, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Therapeutic Communities Act. 1978-1979 (Box 257, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Tort Reform. 1986 (Box 257, Folder 13-21)
        - Courts, Tort Reform. 1986-1990 (Box 257, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Tort Reform. 1986-1992 (Box 257, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Torture Victim Protection Act. 1986 (Box 257, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Tris Flame Retardant Chemical Compensation. 1977 (Box 257, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Unfair Competition Act. 1985 (Box 257, Folder 26)
        - Courts, United States-Canada Free Trade Agreement. 1988 (Box 257, Folder 27)
        - Courts, U.S. Marshals Service. 1977-1981 (Box 257, Folder 28)
        - Courts, U.S. Marshals Service. 1984-1986 (Box 257, Folder 29)
        - Courts, U.S. Marshals Service. 1988-1992 (Box 257, Folder 30)
        - Courts, United States-Mexico Free Trade Agreement. 1991 (Box 257, Folder 31)
        - Courts, Venue Reform. 1980-1984 (Box 257, Folder 32)
        - Courts, Venue Reform. 1984 (Box 257, Folder 33)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. no date (Box 258, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1978 (Box 258, Folder 2-4)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1979 (Box 258, Folder 5-7)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1980 (Box 258, Folder 8-13)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1980-1981 (Box 258, Folder 14)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1980-1982 (Box 258, Folder 15)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1981 (Box 258, Folder 16-17)
        - Courts, Vesco Investigation. 1982 (Box 258, Folder 18-21)
        - Courts, Veterans of Atomic Testing. 1987 (Box 258, Folder 22)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1977-1978 (Box 258, Folder 23)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1982-1984 (Box 258, Folder 24)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1982-1988 (Box 258, Folder 25)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1982-1989 (Box 259, Folder 1)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1984 (Box 259, Folder 2)
        - Courts, Victims of Crime. 1987-1988 (Box 259, Folder 3)
        - Courts, Vietnam Veterans of America, Federal Charter. 1985 (Box 259, Folder 4)
        - Courts, Voir Dire Reform. 1984-1989 (Box 259, Folder 5)
        - Courts, Volunteer Protection Act. 1987-1989 (Box 259, Folder 6)
        - Courts, Volunteer Protection Act. 1987-1990 (Box 259, Folder 7)
        - Courts, Volunteer Protection Act. 1991-1993 (Box 259, Folder 8)
        - Courts, Whistleblower Protection Act. 1989 (Box 259, Folder 9)
        - Courts, Witness Fees. 1977-1978 (Box 259, Folder 10)
        - Courts, Witness Protection/U.S. Marshals. 1984 (Box 259, Folder 11)
        - Courts, Workload Report and Report of Judicial Conference (Bound Volume). 1980 (Box 259, Folder 12)
        - Courts, Workload Report and Report of Judicial Conference (Bound Volume). 1984 (Box 259, Folder 13)
        - Courts, Workload Report and Report of Judicial Conference (Bound Volume). 1985 (Box 259, Folder 14)
      - Judiciary: General, 1975-1994
        - General, Child Abuse Prevention Month. 1982-1985 (Box 259, Folder 15)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1978-1984 (Box 259, Folder 16)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1985-1989 (Box 259, Folder 17)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1985-1993 (Box 260, Folder 1)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1987-1989 (Box 260, Folder 2)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1989-1994 (Box 260, Folder 3)
        - General, Commemorative Legislation. 1991-1994 (Box 260, Folder 4)
        - General, Commission on the Bicentennial of the Constitution. 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 5)
        - General, Committee Agendas. 1980-1988 (Box 260, Folder 6)
        - General, Committee Amendments. 1983 (Box 260, Folder 7)
        - General, Cooper Nomination for Assistant Attorney General. 1985 (Box 260, Folder 8)
        - General, Correspondence. 1975-1979 (Box 260, Folder 9)
        - General, Correspondence. 1978-1980 (Box 260, Folder 10)